笑ってた　狂っていた
I was laughing. I was insane.
絶えず泣きじゃくった
I was crying uncontrollably
忘れてた感情が不安から魔が刺した
The feelings I'd forgotten about stabbed me from anxiety.
歪んでく視界　瞑想
My vision becomes distorted, so I meditate.
動揺は冷め切った
My agitation calms down
忘れてた感情はよくて妄想で埋葬
My forgotton feelings were buried in my imagination
笑ってた　狂っていた
I was laughing. I was crazy.
ただ怯えきっていた
I was terrified.
忘れてた感情はよくて妄想を埋葬
So I buried my forgotten feelings in my imagination.
この眼で
With these eyes
見える映像全て
all of the images I see
求めて
Seeking
すれ違い始めてく
everything begins to separate
奏でて
A song plays
言葉だけ泳いで
only the words swim around
壊れて
Broken
想いが零れ出す
my thoughts spill over
「いつだって会いたい」って
"I've always wanted to see you"
君からそう言われたら
If I heard you say that...
もう何も言えない
I can't say anything
笑ってた　狂っていた
I was laughing. I was insane.
誰と触れ合ったんだ
Who did I come into contact with?
忘れてた感情が不安から魔が刺した
The feelings I'd forgotten about stabbed me from anxiety.
歪んだ儚い幻想
My hallucinations fill me with emptyness
衝動は冷め切った
the urges subside
忘れてた感情はよくて妄想で埋葬
My forgotton feelings were buried in my imagination
この眼で
With these eyes
見える映像全て
all of the images I see
求めて
Seeking
すれ違い始めてく
everything begins to seperate
奏でて
A song plays
言葉だけ泳いで
only the words swim around
壊れて
Broken
想いが零れ出す
my thoughts spill over
「ずっと信じている」って
"I always believed"
君からそう言われたら
If I heard you say that...
もう何も言えない
I can't say anything
笑ってた　狂っていた
I was laughing. I was insane.
ただ怯えきっていた
I was terrified.
忘れてた感情はよくて妄想を埋葬
So I buried my forgotton feelings in my imagination
この眼で
With these eyes
見える映像全て
all of the images I see
求めて
Seeking
すれ違い始めてく
everything begins to separate
奏でて
A song plays
言葉だけ泳いで
only the words swim around
壊れて
Broken
想いが零れ出す
my thoughts spill over
一滴涙だって
One tear.
君が笑ってくれたんだ
Because you smiled for me.
僕は強くなれる
I can become strong.
そんな気がするんだ
I can feel it.